Preliminary Guide to the Blake Smith Papers, 1940-1973
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
Blake Smith papers 1940-1973
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University
Smith, Blake, 1902-1973.
750 items 1.2 linear feet
Baptist minister; pastor of the University Baptist Church, Austin, Texas from 1943-1969.
Radio talks, drafts of sermons, sermon transcripts, and a scrapbook of clippings from Smith's time as a pastor at the University Baptist Church of Austin, Texas. Also includes rosters of University of Texas Baptist students and an article on Darwinism in Texas.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
Gift, 2008 (2008-0296), 1.2 lin. ft.
Biographical / Historical Note
Baptist minister; pastor of the University Baptist Church, Austin, Texas from 1943-1969.
Collection Overview
Radio talks, drafts of sermons, sermon transcripts, and a scrapbook of clippings from Smith's time as a pastor at the University Baptist Church of Austin, Texas. Also includes rosters of University of Texas Baptist students and an article on Darwinism in Texas.
Subject Headings
These and related materials may be found under the following headings in online catalogs.
Baptist Church -- Sermons
Evolution
Ethics
Theology
Smith, Blake, 1902-1973.
University Baptist Church (Austin, Tex.)
Sermons
Contents of Collection
- Accession (2008-0296), 1940-1973, 2 Boxes
  - Radio Talks, 1940s, (2 binders) (Box 1)
    - Transcripts of sermons
    - Rosters of University of Texas Baptist students, 1950s
  - Handwritten sermons, (1 binder)
  - Darwinism in Texas, 1972
  - Radio Talks, 1940s, (2 binders) (Box 2)
  - Scrapbook
    - Sermon scripts
    - Newspaper clippings